for the reporting of an issue in around
the house by a tenant. Uh we have an
intake or sick operations that is done
by [music] a wizard. This is a technical
complicated and requires a lot of
knowledge. What we've created is a
co-pilot solution that [music] can do
the intake based on natural language, an
image or a combination both to uptake
the intake and to create a possible
solution for the fix. We'll start with
going to the realy unit. From there we
can look up a real unit by the address.
From the address, we can uh start the
maintenance [music] intake with copilot.
You can either uh add an image, text or
a combination. In this case, we'll do an
image of a broken [music] door. And
next, uh we'll click generate. So,
copilot can look at the image, analyze
it, [music] and see what possible uh
solutions there are. We can check for
the explanation why it has [music]
chosen that uh task and we can confirm
it. This will create the maintenance
request. Uh and what we can do next is
go to the attachments. uh see the image
that the request was created with and
also see a little bit of an explanation
what the AI is seeing on the image to
give a little bit of a of a look behind
the scenes.